popyard.com 2018-06-29

# PopYard: Today's Science & Technologies.

| 

## Privacy ...

PopYard.com, we value our Site Visitors and Store Members, and respect your right to privacy. We do not engage in SPAM, nor do we share the personal contact information of our stores, visitors, or their friends, relatives, and associates with third parties. The following information provides more detail about our Privacy Policy. 

**Use and Collection of Store and Site Visitor Information**

The only personal information collected by PopYard.com is submitted voluntarily by Site Visitors through email correspondence. Other information collected by PopYard.com includes site usage statistics and click-through information, which is collected electronically as a result of actions taken by Site Visitors. PopYard.com personnel are fully educated about the policies and practices of PopYard.com in regards to protecting voluntarily submitted personal information from outside access, and take every measure possible to prevent unauthorized use or disclosure. 

**Site Usage, Searches and Click-Throughs**

Statistics about site usage, searches and click-throughs gathered by PopYard.com are collected in an aggregate format only. Aggregate statistics about general site usage is collected anonymously. Site Visitors are not personally tracked in any way. 

**Cookies and Log Files**

Cookies are not placed on the systems of Site Visitors to PopYard.com. 

Log file entries are generated when a Site Visitor requests a search at PopYard.com. These entries are generated anonymously, and enable PopYard.com to assess overall site activity, track interest in advertised sales, and troubleshoot technical concerns. Log files are used internally only, and are not associated with any particular user, computer or browser. 

**Third-party Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). The link for "[click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)" is [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). 

**Protection of Site Visitor Information**

Once received by PopYard.com, email submitted voluntarily by Site Visitors is kept absolutely confidential. Access to this information is restricted to PopYard.com administrators, and personally identifiable information contained in the email is only used to respond to the respective query. PopYard.com does not rent, sell or exchange the email addresses of Site Visitors, or of their friends, associates or relatives, to any third party, including its store members. In addition, PopYard.com does not use these email addresses to engage in SPAM activities. Email voluntarily submitted by Site Visitors is removed from our records following its review. 

**Notification of Privacy Policies**

This policy statement informs PopYard.com Site Visitors that PopYard.com will keep their personally identifiable information confidential. 

**Opt-Out / Removal of Information**

Since PopYard.com does not solicit personally identifiable information from site visitors, we do not have an opt-out policy. 

**Use of Site by Minors**

PopYard.com does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. 

PopYard.com further does not promote, condone or endorse the dissemination of information, or sale of products and services to minors when prohibited by law; including the dissemination or sale of pornographic materials to minors; and the sale of firearms, tobacco and alcohol to minors. 

**Site Visitor Interaction with Stores**

The PopYard.com website includes links to third-party websites. PopYard.com has no control over the privacy practices of these websites. Once a Site Visitor has linked from PopYard.com to a third-party website, the visitor is responsible for obtaining Privacy Policy information from the third-party site. 

**Accessing Personal Information**

Since PopYard.com does not collect personally identifiable information from Site Visitors, access is not provided. 

If you have any questions about the Privacy Policy for PopYard.com, please contact us at info@PopYard.com   
  
---|---
